{
    "subject": "resource/All_I_Do_Is_Win",
    "predicate": "property/relyear",
    "object": "2010",
    "human_readable": "All I Do Is Win was released in 2010.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7896823883056641,
            "question": "What year was the song 'All I Do Is Win' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5317352414131165,
            "question": "Has 'All I Do Is Win' won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5119428634643555,
            "question": "Has 'All I Do Is Win' been featured in any movies or television shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5103016495704651,
            "question": "Which artist or group is known for the song 'All I Do Is Win'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4704062044620514,
            "question": "Is 'All I Do Is Win' a popular song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4441029727458954,
            "question": "Are there any notable collaborations on the song 'All I Do Is Win'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42006170749664307,
            "question": "What is the overall theme of the song 'All I Do Is Win'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40960896015167236,
            "question": "Are there any popular remixes or covers of 'All I Do Is Win'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37849727272987366,
            "question": "Where was 'All I Do Is Win' first performed live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3276859521865845,
            "question": "What genre of music does 'All I Do Is Win' belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=All I Do Is Win was released in 2010.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1682_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was 'All I Do Is Win' first performed live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1682_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any popular remixes or covers of 'All I Do Is Win'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1682_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall theme of the song 'All I Do Is Win'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1682_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1682_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that the song \"All I Do Is Win\" by DJ Khaled featuring Ludacris, Rick Ross, Snoop Dogg, and T-Pain was released in 2010."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}